Wanna try 'em on?
I can't afford it.
Becca gave the nod. All yours, no strings.
No thanks.
Didn't bother you
when you put that klepped Sandy on.
Can't scavenge off someone you knew?
They're techie mitts anyways.
You're just being picky.
I have my sights set on something else.
Wha'tcha got your eyes on?
Oh! This?
Bit big for you, ain't it?
I can handle it.
Sure, all yours if I flatline.
Gives you time to bulk up, grow into 'em.
'Kay. Deal.
Ya know, something's different about you…
Huh?
You're usually moping,
bringing the vibe down…
Resident buzzkill.
I'm not!
And I ain't no different from yesterday!
Nah. Something's off.
Ya get laid?
You did.
Gotta work on that poker face, son!
Kiwi! Any progress?
Not at all.
Tanaka's beefed up his defenses
since the last gig.
Tried poking holes around,
but it's been a no-go.
What did I tell ya? We ain't getting
nowhere unless Faraday feeds us something.
Tanaka?
Remember your very first grand theft auto?
He's the owner of the limo.
Problem?
Nah, it's nothing…
Would you look at that.
You were schoolmates with Tanaka's kid.
What?! You accusing our kid of
going to some stuffy corpo school?!
Bona-fide Arasaka Academy dropout.
Straight A student, too.
I'll be damned!
Guess we now know why Gloria was
always strapped on cash.
What's a guy gotta do
to get some privacy around here?
There's not much else I could find on
Tanaka's private file. The rest is trash.
-Like?
-XBDs in his viewing log.
That's good. We can use it for leverage.
A real kinkster. More gore than porn.
Some cyberpsycho shit, too.
The deep, dark fetishes of a suit.
Lots of vids from a gonk who goes by JK.
JK?
Heard of him?
Sure. Jimmy Kurosaki. The braindance
director with a cult following.
He's known for putting up snuff reels
within 24 hours of it happening.
Never seen any director
do the edits that he does.
No wonder he's got so many fans.
Didn't know you were a superfreak.
Uh, well…
Just helped a choom
move his stock, is all.
That's good and all, but do you have
any intel we can actually use?
They're custom-made.
What?
I heard that he sometimes tunes
custom-made footage for VIPs.
You know, like removing pain limiters?
So what?
If he's tuning the footage,
Tanaka's gotta be there as well.
And probably alone.
Alone? How you figure?
Would you bring a bodyguard
to tune up a fetish BD?
Kid's got a point.
Getting sharp, kid!
Now that you're a man now!
What? Did something happen?
Nothing!
Faraday came through
with a lead on Tanaka.
Seems our favorite suit
occasionally ditches his huscle
and usual ride for a Delamain.
Going off-radar, huh?
But Delamain's got him fully covered.
Still can't pinpoint his destination.
I also looked into
the tuning services for BDs.
The main buyers are fat cats,
corpo execs, celebrities, gang bosses…
You get in by referral
and the location is undisclosed.
If we wanna know more,
we'd have to chat with the man himself.
How?
Gotta grab him in person.
Lucky for us, he has a reservation at
Embers tomorrow. He'll be alone.
At a ritzy place like that? Sad.
Great. When he leaves,
let's invite him here for a nightcap.
Let's go.
Hey! You wouldn't happen to be
Jimmy Kurosaki, would you?
Who's asking?
I knew it! I'm a huge fan, sir!
You know a ripperdoc
in Arroyo who pushes XBDs?
I helped him sell your stuff!
Really.
Can I shake your hand?
Oh, sorry… Guess I'm a bit star-struck.
Yeah, I got places to be.
Right… I won't hold you up.
Was an honor meeting you…
What was that?!
Fuck!
What?!
Maine!
Where's David?
Find him!
Snap out of it!
You alright?
Son of a bitch pulled something on us.
What happened?
They're gone.
Gone?
He nabbed David.
Kiwi! You take Maine and head out.
Okay.
I'm fine…
Be a good boy, and stay!
Lucy! You're with me.
Got him. Mile and change, straight ahead.
What did that asshole use back there?
Seemed like some kind of EMP.
It got Kiwi real bad.
Only gave me a bit of a shock.
Neural implant targeting.
To neutralize runners, clearly.
You seem okay.
I wasn't in range.
David could be in real shit.
It'll be a problem if he uses that again.
Not if we kill him first.
You're pissed, aren't ya?
A little.
Ah, fuck.
Think it's a cyberpsycho?
No shit, let's head out.
Already hailed MaxTac.
Hey, there's another body.
Don't wander off, man.
What if you run into them?
Don't worry. They're not around anymore.
Hm? Who's there?!
The cyberpsycho!
He's got a gun!
-It wasn't me…
-Drop the gun!
Don't move!
-I woke up and I was just…
-Drop it, you fucking psycho!
Who's there?!
Hey! What happened?!
Got a cyberpsycho!
Raise MaxTac now!
Shots fired back there!
Die, bastard!
MaxTac?!
Fucking monster.
No! It wasn't me!
Awesome, isn't it?
Experiencing your own death
instead of someone else's.
Are you fucking kidding me?!
Awesome? You fucking psychopath…
Hey, I thought you were a fan!
Most of my fans are whack jobs.
You're a cyberpunk, aren't you?
What are you after?
Ambushing me in a place like that…
Clearly, you've done your homework.
Have you seen any of my other works?
The Edgerunner series?
Yeah.
I've seen most of your stuff.
Wow. I'm flattered!
Say, have you ever wondered
where I get those cyberpsycho scrolls?
What?
All military prototypes come with
a built-in braindance scroller.
Some people are willing to
pay through the nose for that kinda stuff.
You know who originally owned this Sandy?
James Norris. How many people
did he kill in the end? 27?
Had a hell of a run-in
with MaxTac in the end.
It's not often you get a guy
who can go toe-to-toe with them.
That was so good…
One of the best I've seen in a while.
I've got high expectations for you, too.
I'm surprised you're still sane
after wearing this.
The side-effects are gonna
drive you mad, eventually.
Can't wait to see it.
I'm not gonna go psycho!
That's what all chromers say.
They think they're all sane
until they aren't.
Not me!
Yes, you.
Another couple rounds with the MaxTac
and your brain'll burst like a balloon.
Wait. You're not gonna
make me go through that again…
Hey, stop!
Cut it out!
Stop!
Don't move!
Put your hands up…
Or you're dead.
You got me!
How's David?
He's in a BD or something.
-Can you get him out?
-I'll try.
Need a hand?
Shut it!
Got it!
David! You alright?
Aw, what a shame.
So? What do you guys want?
I assume you're not here to kill me.
That's still up for jury.
Come on. I'll cooperate.
You catch on quick.
That better not be…
Armed drones!
Bingo!
Call them off!
No can do.
Go on, give 'em a wave.
They're my best toys. Bulletproof and all.
Good luck putting them down
with those tiny little bangers.
I'll blow your brains out first!
Well, that wouldn't be very smart.
That won't stop them from turning you
into a bloodstain on my floor.
Yeah? They won't shoot as long as
I'm using you as a meat-shield.
Knew it was smart to have two.
Shit!
Oh no! Looks like you're surrounded.
Ready to give up?
Shut up!
Lucy!
On it…
I need more time…
David!
I'll distract them!
Hurry it up, Lucy!
Wow! That was impressive!
-Mother…
-Fucker!
White flag! White flag!
Okay, I surrender for real this time!
White flag my ass!
You're already dead, shit stain!
I mean, alright, but I thought
you wanted to ask me things?
God dammit!
Hey girl! Takes real talent
to pull off a hack so quickly.
I'll listen to what you have to say,
but can I get up, please?
No funny business or I'll kill you myself.
I won't. Pinky swear.
Alright. Everyone got the plan?
Aye aye, captain.
I'll call you later.
Until then, stay here.
Keep an eye on him.
Don't let him out of your sight.
Sorry about earlier.
Whatever.
Didn't think you'd agree
to help us so easily.
I know how cyberpunks work.
I don't really have a choice, do I?
Well, yeah.
You've seen that one too?
Yeah.
You saw it
and you still installed the Sandy?
You're one crazy dude.
I won't end up like him.
James Norris was a soldier
who knew his way around implants.
But even he couldn't take it
and went psycho.
What makes you think you're different?
I don't know. It just… feels right.
It's like the implant's
always been a part of me.
I think… I'm built different.
You think you're special?
Sure.
I've seen plenty of chromejocks
go psycho over the years.
Some metal's simply not meant to
mix with meat.
Your organic body, your soul, gets pushed
to the edge. Teeters on the brink.
It always comes down to one of two things.
You either lose your mind…
Or die… No in-between.
We will be arriving
at the destination shortly.
As requested, the record of
your ride today has been expunged.
I look forward to serving you again.
Hey, Mister Tanaka. Come on in.
You're early.
It usually takes months for a new release.
Well, it's difficult finding
good material, you see.
But this next one'll be worth your while.
Would you like to have it
tuned immediately?
My son is being discharged
from the hospital tonight.
I will just be taking the chip.
I see.
That's unfortunate. I'm proud of
how this one turned out.
It'd be a huge waste not to have it tuned.
The sensitivity'd be off the charts.
Mister Kurosaki.
I do not humor slow men.
Unfortunate's one word for it.
Would've made our job a lot easier
if you were in that BD.
Who are you?
Don't try nothing.
The nerve…
Super sorry, sir.
They have me by the balls.
Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with?
Forget about the panic button.
We've got a jammer up.
Just as planned, I see.
Not fucking now!
Maine!
You're…
Pain in my ass.
Must've been the needles.
Got him in the neck.
Shit, he really was slow.
He's suffocating.
Ah… Sucks for him.
Looks like he won't be around
to edit his own death scroll.
Flatlined.
Shit. Trauma Team's coming.
What? This bitch had Trauma coverage?
Yup. Platinum and everything.
Fuck.
Kid, we're getting the hell out!
Now. They find us and we're fucked.